Guide to the William Webster Hansen Papers
Stanford University. Libraries.
- NO TITLE -handwritten notebook, undated (Box 13, Folder 168[E-7])
- NO TITLE -notebook dated, 1939 (Box 13, Folder 169[?K-10E])
- W.W. HANSEN, PHYSICS DEPT. (Box 13, Folder 170[M-5])
  notebooks, graphs, data sheets (?) dated 1939
- NO TITLE -handwritten notebook (Box 13, Folder 171[I-12])
- W.W. HANSEN, PHYSICS DEPT. -handwritten notebook (Box 13, Folder 172[K-10D])
- Microwave Lecture Notes, 1944; 3 vols. (Box 14)
- NOTEBOOK FOR PHYSICS 105/106, (1945-1948)
  - Preliminary notes (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Physics 106: experiment 3, Rydberg constant (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Physics 105: experiment 13, Boltzmann's constant (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Modern physics, fall, 1946-47 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Physics 105: oil drop experiment (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Physics 106: e/m experiment (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Physics 105/106: experiment 4 - gravitation constant (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Physics 106: thermionic emission (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Physics 106: velocity of light (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Physics 106: cloud chamber (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - Miscellaneous notes and final exam (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - Modern Physics, outlines, 1946 - (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - syllabus, lab groups, and experiment/lecture notes, Spring 1948: (Box 15, Folder 13)
- NOTEBOOK, (1940)
  - Modern Physics (Box 15, Folder 14)
- Scans of the 3 volumes located in Box 14 (Microwave lecture notes), Accession ARCH-2009-059; 8 optical disc(s) (DVD) (Box 1)